[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'でんとうぶんか' read in word?",
        "answer": "Традиційна культура"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ごらく' read in word?",
        "answer": "розваги"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さどう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Чайна церемонія"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おちゃ' read in word?",
        "answer": "чай"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'みち' read in word?",
        "answer": "шлях"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょどう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Каліграфія"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かぶき' read in word?",
        "answer": "Кабукі"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'のう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Театр Но"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぶんらく' read in word?",
        "answer": "Театр Бунраку"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'すもう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Сумо"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'じゅうどう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Дзюдо"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けんどう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Кендо"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'からて' read in word?",
        "answer": "Карате"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'まんざい' read in word?",
        "answer": "Комедійний діалог на сцені・Ракуґо (комічне естрадне оповідання)"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'らくご' read in word?",
        "answer": "Комедійний діалог на сцені・Ракуґо (комічне естрадне оповідання)"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いご' read in word?",
        "answer": "Ґо"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょうぎ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Сьоги"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'パチンコ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Ігровий автомат"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぼんおどり' read in word?",
        "answer": "Танець на фестиваль “Бон”"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おどり' read in word?",
        "answer": "Танець"
    }
]